{
  "LevelId": 11,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 99,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "VOLATILE",
      "question": "Unstable and unpredictable"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "OVERSEAS",
      "question": "places located in foreign countries, typically across the sea"
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "PLATFORM",
      "question": "surface or stage used as a base for various activities or technologies"
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BEDROOMS",
      "question": "Personal sleeping spaces"
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "IDENTITY",
      "question": "Unique personal traits and characteristics"
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "PERIODIC",
      "question": "Recurring at regular intervals"
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BLOSSOMS",
      "question": "Flower in bloom"
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "FIGHTING",
      "question": "act of engaging in a physical or verbal conflict with someone"
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "JUDICIAL",
      "question": "Relating to the legal system or courts"
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "PROPERTY",
      "question": "term refers to possessions or belongings that someone owns"
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "LEADERSHIP",
      "question": "ability to guide, direct, or influence others in a positive direction"
    }
  ]
}